<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>live2home on Sauca Live Light</title><link>https://www.saucalivelight.com/tags/live2home/</link><description>Recent content in live2home on Sauca Live Light</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:02:56 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.saucalivelight.com/tags/live2home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thanking you all at Plasa Focus 2023!</title><link>https://www.saucalivelight.com/post/postleeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:02:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.saucalivelight.com/post/postleeds/</guid><description>Thanking you all at Plasa Focus 2023!
We at Sauca Live Light were delighted to spend the time meeting industry friends as well as so many inspiring new creatives and technical talents in Leeds. So very many exciting and vibrant conversations about where these new and immersive lighting possibilities will take us and so many good ideas of applications we had never thought of!
Our Sauca Live Light lovely and homely living room, really enjoyed your many visits and being able to show you our unique new development “Live to Home” where human created, lighting designer &amp;ldquo;Scripts&amp;rdquo; can be delivered to your home via the internet, to create immersive ambient lighting environments that accompany your movie, gig, game or audio book to dramatic effect!</description></item><item><title>Sauca Live Light Returns to The Royal Armouries</title><link>https://www.saucalivelight.com/post/plasaleeds2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 05:42:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.saucalivelight.com/post/plasaleeds2023/</guid><description>Once again Sauca Live Light will be exhibiting at Plasa Focus Leeds. Returning to the Royal Armouries we will once again be showcasing our award winning Live to Crowd technology.
Also for the first time we will be demonstrating our unique and patented technology to bring professionally curated lighting streams into your home to generate a truly Hybrid Viewing experience.
Come and visit us to see more on Stand: N-C28</description></item><item><title>Introducing a Revolution in Hybrid Viewing</title><link>https://www.saucalivelight.com/post/live2home/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:09:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.saucalivelight.com/post/live2home/</guid><description>We at Sauca Live Light are poised to launch yet another, new and totally unique technology to the entertainment industry at Plasa Leeds 2023!
Our recently patented technology represents the next significant step in the Sauca development roadmap, and we can guarantee that nothing like this has ever been seen before.
Sauca’s founder and innovative powerhouse, Simon Carter, has wowed us again with his insight and forward thinking in creating this new and ingenious development that will take the art of entertainment lighting into the domestic environment for all to enjoy.</description></item></channel></rss>